ipmart.com 2018-12-26

# ipmart.com.my :: Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. We believe that by respecting your privacy we will earn the opportunity to build a lasting relationship with you, your business, your clients and your staff. Any information you provide to us will only be used for the purpose for which it was intended. We collect your information primarily for proof, contact and billing purposes. Under no circumstances will your information be shared with, or sold to, or disclosed to any third party, except where required by law. This Privacy Policy applies only to information gathered in connection with IPmart.com's consumer credit card accounts used for transactions at IPmart.com and applications for those accounts.

In order to enhance our ability to provide you with the best services, opportunities, and choices possible, we collect, use, and share certain information about you. This policy explains what information we collect and with whom we share it with. The practices described in this policy are applicable to current and former customers and consumers who do business with us. The policy also explains how we protect the security and confidentiality of our customer's information. 

**Information we collect and sources of information.**

We may collect information about some of your personal details and documents, (such as, address, copy of credit card statements, identification, etc) to help us process the order in which you've made, and for us to assure and prove that you are the person paying for the products.

**Marketing OPT-IN and OPT-OUT provision**

When you register, you will be given the option to opt-out of subscribing to our regular update service. We will send you e mail alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about IPmart.com, our subsidiaries or selected business partners. 

We do not sell or otherwise pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes. Marketing communications you subscribe to will only be sent by IPmart.com. 

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that subscription. Simply follow the indications in the e-mail.

**Information we share with service providers or joint marketers.**

We may disclose some of the information we collect, to companies that perform services on our behalf, including those who assist us in selling, billing, shipping and responding to customer inquiries. We may provide that information to others who perform marketing services for us and to financial institutions with whom we jointly offer financial products or services, subject to any requirements and restrictions of applicable law.

**Security and confidentiality of your information.**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know in order to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal and state law standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

**Order and credit card Information**

IPmart.com uses Global Collect, a third-party provider of e-commerce solutions, to power the IPmart.com store and in doing so, collects information about users, including credit card information. When a user purchases a product from the IPmart.com store, Global Collect provides information about the customer, including name, address and email address, to IPmart Network. IPmart Network uses this information as set out in the end user agreement, agreed to by purchasers at the time of purchase. In particular, IPmart Network uses the information to license the software to you, support the software and send you information about updates, upgrades and new works or services provided by IPmart Network.

Global Collect requests information from the user on the order form, viewed by the user as a page hosted on the Global Collect web server. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used as explained above. For example, if we have trouble processing an order, contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

Your credit card information does not pass through the Global Collect sites under the terms of IPmart's agreement with Global Collect. Global Collect does not share credit card information with IPmart Network. Global Collect keeps your credit card information confidential and protect your credit card information through the use of industry-standard Secure Sockets (SSL) encryption technology. 

**Where and how to ask question or file complaints**

If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the Customer Service and FAQ section of the web site where frequently asked questions (FAQ's) are answered. If you require more information please go to the Customer Service section of the web site and send an email to the relevant IPmart.com department. If you wish to talk to a IPmart.com customer care representative please call 03-21100277 or 03-21416750 or write to: Customer Service, I-Pmart Network (M) Sdn Bhd, Suite A & C, Level 6 Annexe Block, Amoda Building, 22, Jalan Imbi, 55100 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. You can also email us at [support@ipmart.com.my](mailto:support@ipmart.com.my).
